my name is Jean I'm 26 and interesting
thing about me I am here doing an
interview with you right now oh that is
interesting this is a great show and
you're really lucky to be here so what
makes you the most angry in this world
um I would say online selfies in the
bathrooms what about that makes you
angry the thought that there's
behind that person yes and the fact that
you could have moved one room over to
your bedroom right move to that bedroom
speaking of bedrooms do you want to know
what makes me the most angry what I hate
when you're making out with a girl and
she's like sucking on your neck and then
it bursts the blood vessels and it's
like I'm 26 years old baby I don't need
a hickey you know I don't know what
you're talking about what's that over
there
what
what what